
Speaker 1  (00:00)
This is just kind of me thinking out loud so don't really don't really take anything. I have to say for different deaths definitely But so we could have cancer. The junk like shelves. 

Speaker 2  (00:14)
Jars. 

Speaker 1  (00:17)
And then you can categorize So I'm The problem is I launched. I want the thing to be based around jars. I want the app to be based on drugs. 

Speaker 1  (00:37)
So you have jars of information There is also the whole aspect of there is multiple different apps in the app. Basically. So do you have like 

Speaker 3  (00:53)
Jars. 

Speaker 1  (00:54)
That can be different categories, and you're only allowed to put those Categories. 

Speaker 3  (01:03)
Like, you have a jar for notes a jar for to do a jar for reminders and arford budgets. 

Speaker 1  (01:08)
Living and you can only put those things in your jars or do you just make? I think I think budgeting is gonna be a separate thing. I don't think budgeting is gonna be in jars. 

Speaker 1  (01:20)
Or do you just have only notes in your notes? 

Speaker 1  (01:36)
This is difficult because Maybe. Because I feel like if you have jars of notes. That's not really like A And this is hard. 

Speaker 1  (02:04)
Because I'm already really set on the jars idea I really like jars. I love jars. Maybe I have to maybe I have to undo charge. 

Speaker 1  (02:24)
Or maybe you could just be called jars. There's a whole idea, is it's in everything app. But how do you make it? 

Speaker 1  (02:43)
Everything abdominal. With jars. So I have a few ideas. 

Speaker 1  (02:51)
We could do you just have jars of different categories? And then budgeting is separate, or you have jars of different categories, and budgeting is part of the jars, and you can just kind of put Ooh ohh, maybe oh wait hold on. Maybe you have different shelves of categories. 

Speaker 1  (03:10)
And then you put your things in the jars, and then budgeting would have to be separate. Budgeting would be its own thing. Budgeting would be like. 

Speaker 1  (03:19)
Like a separate tab down at the bottom for everything else. I feel like because I feel like budgeting. Isn't really something you can just put into a jar. 

Speaker 1  (03:27)
I feel like that's more of like a category of jars. If anything so, we'll have budgeting budgeting is separate. So what we're gonna do is we're gonna we're integrate, budgeting later is what I'm saying. 

Speaker 1  (03:40)
So We have budgeting a separate that's that's amazing. So now that I know that I've decided that budgeting is gonna be separate. We can do different shelves, so there can be a tap on the bottom. 

Speaker 1  (03:56)
You can have my shelves, my budget And settings, the settings is definitely going to be a big part. This is going to be a very configurable app that's one of the main things that I'm trying to go for very configurable. So you have my jars, my budget and settings, and then my or sorry, my shelf. 

Speaker 1  (04:16)
And then in your shelf, you can have different categories of shelves. And You can put Different jars. In the shelves. 

Speaker 1  (04:37)
And then the jars could be your notes. But then you would also have My reminder's And might do Oh, that doesn't really make sense, doesn't 

Speaker 1  (05:02)
But yeah. Because I want the idea is that it's in everything out Like it will, it? Does everything I mean I might even call it jar? 

Speaker 1  (05:16)
OS? 

Speaker 2  (05:17)
No. 

Speaker 1  (05:19)
Kate, I really like the drawer idea. But I might have to scrap that Because that is kind of Vul Because I want it to be like your hub for everything. Like it's the everything happens. 

Speaker 1  (05:52)
Maybe we could just call it the everything happen. No, I don't like that. I really like the jars idea. 

Speaker 1  (06:00)
I really, because that's like my idea And it's like, I think it's a good idea. So I really want to try and stick with jars, although I am not completely opposed to changing the whole thing up But maybe we could have Your jars be. Your thoughts and ideas and notes. 

Speaker 1  (06:24)
And then you just happen to have This is difficult, I'm gonna need some. I'm gonna need some other feedback. So I'm gonna definitely need to have some other decisions. 

Speaker 1  (06:46)
But I definitely do really want to stick with the jars idea, we could just have it be jars. 

Speaker 2  (06:53)
Has it acquired? 

Speaker 1  (06:57)
This is difficult because it's We did have Budgeting is going to be separate. That's the determinant, but it's still going to be in jars. Jars, is the aptaine remember So we could have Budgeting, my budget settings. 

Speaker 1  (07:36)
And then we could just have jars. We could just have my like my jars tab. And that would be like Your place to make reminders move Or maybe the app is a single jar. 

Speaker 1  (08:04)
Yeah, maybe you think of it as a single jar? Oh, we could just call it jar. 

Speaker 1  (08:26)
Yeah, it could be a single jar. And then the homepage could be the tab at the bottom could be my jar, and then you would have my budget. And then you can have inside of my jar. 

Speaker 1  (08:40)
You would have a note section to do section. And we can also probably just get rid of my budget section and put that in the in my jar. And then you can pin whatever you decide to at the bottom. 

Speaker 1  (08:52)
Okay, okay I like where we're going with that. I will definitely continue that. Because that is not a bad idea. 
