
Speaker 1  (00:00)
Okay, okay, here we go. So the success air recording to get some thoughts stand on my app. I'm Eric Benjamin Hubert. 

Speaker 1  (00:11)
This is being our friend on Usually, January 6th 2026. Um, so my idea for my app is You, it's like a it's like a everything app. I don't know. 

Speaker 1  (00:26)
I don't know who this recording is going to be going to. And I know it's probably going to be going to Claude. So this is kind of like a repivo It's almost like a stage 2 Of the based budgeting app I don't really know what I want to call the new version of the app quite yet. 

Speaker 1  (00:49)
It probably should get a better logo in mind. But that's kind of a afterthought, so right now, it would just be called The we'll just cut name it. The app, we'll just coname it the app that's perfect. 

Speaker 1  (01:10)
So I want this app to do a few things because One of the Nova, most annoying Things about, you know, living just keeping track of things just in general. And so I made the budget app If that really helped me keep track of my finances. You know, there's a bunch of other c*** that I wanna keep track of. 

Speaker 1  (01:32)
So I was just thinking to myself. What if I make Hey? Like a better Better apps, better. 

Speaker 1  (01:45)
I feel like a better platform, I guess to do all of this keeping track of So my idea is If you first booted up And you tell it what you want to keep track of so the main things that it's going to do the app is going to do. Your codename app codename V app. The main thing is it's gonna do is it's going to Yeah, being note taking up Okay so I want to. 

Speaker 1  (02:16)
I'm sure there's already like open source C protocolity type of things for note, taking whatever. That I want to Brian program, my own protocol or have Claude. Do it or whatever I'm gonna be. 

Speaker 1  (02:33)
Even though I'm not that proud of it, I'm gonna be completely transparent and say most of the will probably be coded by cloud. So whoever listens to this You know, giving billions of visitors through my app is so big. Most of this probably will be closed by Claude. 

Speaker 1  (02:51)
I'm just gonna be honest. I'll do all the integration and stuff that I can't do. But if Claude can do it Assume that quad did it I'm probably going to do the more creative V. 

Speaker 1  (03:03)
Creative side of things But other than that clogged would probably do most of most of it, but anyways Needs to be a note taking app. And then a new list The reminder's app. A budget tracking app And then any, and then it used to be able to be modular, because eventually down the road as Their own like kind of module things down the on the app. 

Speaker 1  (03:41)
So it's like 

Speaker 2  (03:45)
We'll start up as 

Speaker 1  (03:46)
Can I track her out? And then you'll be able to get people will be able to with my approvals. It will have to be. 

Speaker 1  (03:57)
It won't be communicated as I feel like, I mean, maybe someday it might be. We've had this current stage. I feel like community guided. 

Speaker 1  (04:08)
Wouldn't be the best idea? Because it's I mean, I know the whole thing is like open source, you know yeah, woohoo but I mean, I don't know, I just think for right now. You probably shouldn't even think about that, but anyways So it's going to be a note, taking flash budgeting/ Can you app? 

Speaker 1  (04:38)
And it needs to do little things very well. We can use the framework that we have from the budgeting app in based budgeting because that will be easy to integrate. Because we already have, you know, the whole thing set up for that. 

Speaker 1  (04:53)
But Hallie set the center of recording this So Well I haven't decided yet if we're gonna we like re. 3 do the color base or whatever on the budgeting app, or if we're gonna make an entirely different refill. And then just let people use the Budgeting app, you know whatever But anyways. 

Speaker 1  (05:31)
We're going to do that. Yeah, there's probably gonna be long pauses in between this recording. Because I am currently at work. 

Speaker 1  (05:39)
And I don't want people to hear me talking. So prepare for long pause 

Speaker 1  (06:30)
Okay, I'm back of course. Um, so we have II guess I don't really know what this app category even would be. But anyways, the I got gosh, my thoughts are everywhere. 

Speaker 1  (06:46)
Dude, so the basis of the app is I guess I mean I could be it could be productivity app, but the basis of the app is There's like an everything app. It can do. You know, lots of different Beams, that pertain to I guess productivity is what you would call it. 

Speaker 1  (07:20)
So it needs to be able to we'll use the framework from the budgeting app and I kind of want to have that same theme. But I also want you to be able to I'm not sure if you could use C. Yes. 

Speaker 1  (07:31)
S or We could make a whole Like sing for Steven, I want you to be able to make your own themes basically for the entire app. And we're gonna start with We're going to start with He needs to be So I guess, oh gosh gosh dude, if I'm ever good at this Let's go okay. How far are we into this recording? 

Speaker 1  (08:00)
I guess I should probably check. No, my gosh, 8 minutes dude. Okay, we're back headed. 

Speaker 1  (08:08)
Check how long that would be. So I guess I will tell. What the what I want the end? 

Speaker 1  (08:16)
Goal to be so, the end goal is to have an app. That. You can use to Record budgeting. 

Speaker 1  (08:28)
A notes app. I'm A Now to-do list app. And a reminder's app. 

Speaker 1  (08:40)
It needs to be able to connect to the clouds somehow, in a secure encrypted way that's a very important detail. It must be secure and encrypted and whatever service I decide to use or if I decide to you know, go to the heavy route and program my own service, it needs to be secure and encrypted. So we're gonna learn how that works. 

Speaker 1  (09:01)
That's gonna be. Definitely an interesting prospect of this whole thing, but that probably won't be until later, until yeah, I mean, yeah, that probably won't be until later. But he needs to be able to Keep track of finances budgets. 

Speaker 1  (09:18)
And then also be a note, taking app a reminder's app. And a to do wasdap, because Elizabeth's like productivity But. Uh U. 

Speaker 1  (09:29)
You should do that and then you used to look nice I think you should be able to export all my data and see how I guess I am using my data. We're gonna start with An Android app. 

Speaker 1  (09:55)
We will start with an Android app. It's because I feel like that's probably the easiest to make, and that's what I need the most right now. But we'll start with an Android app. 

Speaker 1  (10:08)
It needs to be fast, but I guess I guess one of the main things no python is gonna know that python is kind of a slower language which would be coding in. Fandom. We mostly, you know, native to the platform. 

Speaker 1  (10:23)
So if we're doing Android, first mostly cotland based And then if we decide to do my next priority would probably be a desktop Linux version for each major distribution. Not like an app invention. We need to be each major distribution. 

Speaker 1  (10:38)
So that would be Fedora, a boon 2 dvin. Arch and then I guess anything else that exists out there. It used to be able for that. 

Speaker 1  (10:49)
So whatever the native language is for that. And then windows would probably be come later. But it needs to be able to You're the app. 

Speaker 1  (11:01)
And it needs to obviously open source. You know, you know, me open source. But my main thing is, it needs to just be able to. 

Speaker 1  (11:09)
I've said this so many times and I've holy c***. It's a very scissors near It is a budgeting. I'm just making sure whoever's listening to this. 

Speaker 1  (11:23)
It's a very clear Idea in their mind. Of what I am trying to make So it needs to be a fed, ran Like how base budgeting is That's kind of the first thing. So what I'll probably do Is I will keep the butt the bath budgeting repo when GitHub But okay, gosh, I get this off-topic. 

Speaker 1  (11:50)
No. We'll expand it there. Bixby budging app. 

Speaker 1  (11:55)
A note taking app. A Reminder's app. And in A View list. 

Speaker 1  (12:09)
I guess reminder in to-do list would go in kind of the same. You know jar, ooh, that's A It's a cool idea. We could fully up grs. 

Speaker 1  (12:27)
And it would be like storing your mind I do any of this. We'll think of branding later, because that's really not a video thing right now. So just one last time budgeting Okay? 

Speaker 1  (12:44)
Ohh, my gosh budgeting to-do list planner, like I'm a reminder and a note taking up I know those are all kind of Very different categories, and I might split them up into, like A I'll probably end up splitting them up. And all that fun stuff. I might be better because then we could have like Yeah, and now that I'm thinking about this. 

Speaker 1  (13:17)
You can kind of having some cool ideas. So one idea that I'll spit by here. Pause. 

Speaker 1  (13:46)
I wanted you that I will kind of. Straight up here is Okay. 

Speaker 1  (14:32)
Alright. Okay. I am currently in my closet. 

Speaker 1  (14:34)
It might be kind of hard to hear me, but one of the ideas that I was this spit behind, is it's We have the jars of 

Speaker 2  (14:45)
And as the whole thing with guys is that it will be transparent. So you'll be able to 

Speaker 1  (14:50)
See like all your 

Speaker 2  (14:51)
Information. Now that's that so, have the jars hub. 

Speaker 1  (14:58)
Because I can't do the enrichment center because 

Speaker 2  (15:00)
It's like a valve thing. But yeah, we'll have the jars hub. And It will you will have the different apps and you can either install the jars hub as a full app, so we'll call it jives, hub. 

Speaker 1  (15:18)
No, I don't know. 

Speaker 2  (15:20)
But we have a hub, and you can decide to install just individual apps or the budget. A after not taking app all that stuff, or you can decide to install the entire hub and it will connect all to each other. They've ever seen it, do it locally. 

Speaker 1  (15:33)
I'm just saying 

Speaker 2  (15:35)
But I think obsidian Is there some is some 

Speaker 1  (15:40)
Some productivity out, I think it might be a subsidian or something else that can think between devices equally. I don't know how it does that, but it needs to be local. It needs to my number one priority with The new car name is going to be jars. 

Speaker 1  (15:57)
Pause. 

Speaker 1  (16:13)
The defendant was falsified another kid. 

Speaker 1  (16:32)
You're gonna have to be a little quieter because there is people in the hospital, but anyways So we have death hub. That sounds weird or just okay. But we'll have like the main the main center Where you can I download. 

Speaker 1  (16:53)
Oh, my gosh dude. I have so many ideas for this. So I guess for stage. 

Speaker 1  (17:00)
From stage one of the app of jars, you're gonna we're gonna codam it to jars. Hey, Jonathan of jars. It is, it's going to be In note, taking a for the 50 billionth time note, taking budgeting. 

Speaker 1  (17:19)
The new list and reminder app. That's the basics. That's what I want stage one of jars to be. 

Speaker 1  (17:28)
And then stage 2 of jars. Well, I got stage. One will also include making it the Android app. 

Speaker 1  (17:34)
Because I need to be able to You know, do this all on my phone? The main main thing that people are really going to download. But then After so that stage one just making the basic app. 

Speaker 1  (17:52)
So H2 would be I guess I guess we should probably talk about stage one app. Features? The jars. 

Speaker 1  (18:04)
Hq or tage, one features a beast, importing and exporting all of your data or data from Data from different Holy c***. I don't know if you can tell, but I am not very good at you know. Ideas getting my ideas straight. 

Speaker 1  (18:34)
So we have the We're just going to call up the productivity. Whenever I say, productivity assume that I am talking about budget tracking budgeting. I'm not taking reminders and to-do list. 

Speaker 1  (18:50)
That's what I say when productivity, so we have the productivity, main portion of And then you, this is all stage. One features the productivity, main portion of it and then you need to be able to export and import your data from each of the individual. Modules So the notes the budgeting, whatever You need to be able to import and export that if things get, you know, deleted or whatever or you need. 

Speaker 1  (19:18)
Just need to make a new account. Whatever comes up, you can do And then There needs to be a light on a Dark mode. There needs to be Android based. 

Speaker 1  (19:31)
So we're gonna first focus on nars Android. Whereas for Android There's to be light in a Dark mode. You should be all open source. 

Speaker 1  (19:45)
All local because of the 2 big things. 3 big things that are local, open source and private. I guess local and private go hand in hand but whatever local open source and private. 

Speaker 1  (19:58)
Under the AGP L version 3 license, I think it was But those are the main 3 requirements. Then, obviously all the productivity stuff needs to have good theming good food. If you're done, you'd Android theming, so it needs to follow Your phone's material, you design this reminder. 

Speaker 1  (20:19)
This is on stage one. So stage one's gonna probably be broken up into different parts of stages. Because I have big ideas. 

Speaker 1  (20:28)
So it needs to look good even for stage one. Because my biggest, my biggest thing is UI and UX So if it doesn't look good day, one Then, it started good album. If I have to wait for things to start looking good and start warping. 

Speaker 1  (20:44)
Good Then, it's not a good app. So if I'm gonna scrutinize that for every other app then I'm going to scrutinize that from the other So we'll do that. That's a lot of breath. 

Speaker 1  (21:06)
So we have productivity. Good good you buy and U. X. 

Speaker 1  (21:12)
Privacy open source. Local importing exportin Another thing is even though Obviously being transparent can be mostly coated with cloud. So AI will have no AI. 

Speaker 1  (21:36)
Pluggins. Unless I guess that's more of a stage. Two thing. 

Speaker 1  (21:40)
But we will have no AI stuff at all. Until later, stages probably So I guess that's the main thing, the productivity theming importing exporting privacy, local and open source. So That's my idea for the app. 

Speaker 1  (21:59)
I have to stop recording now. Because I don't have any more prevatory record. But. 

Speaker 1  (22:05)
It's definitely a doozy, and they really cannot keep my idea straight. And the whole reason trying to make this app is so that, oh maybe. Okay, well, okay? 

Speaker 1  (22:15)
It'd be another thing as a voice recording. Whatever Yeah, that's my that's my idea. I'm definitely interesting. 

Speaker 1  (22:27)
Guys. 

Speaker 3  (22:30)
Governments are coming. 
